I. Feinberg, Robert Arbitration Records 5548
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- [*1975C&D] Miscellaneous arbitration matters settled or withdrawn before hearings., 1969-1971 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  Arranged alphabetically by employer.
- [*1975E-H] Miscellaneous arbitration matters settled or withdrawn before hearings., 1972-1975 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- [*F298A&B] Royal Mink, Inc. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  This file contains materials relating to an unresolved "fur" arbitration case. Of importance is the voluminous documentation of the actions between the two parties in the state courts.